ARINOLA SAHEED OLAMIDE 28 ANIPELE STREET, MUSHIN, LAGOS STATE, NIGERIA 08163770228, 08092138499 ARINOLA_SAHEED@YAHOO.COM

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To find a challenging position in your reputable institution that will utilize both my educational background and professional experience to contribute to the organization's noble and humanitarian goals and simultaneously provide excellent opportunities for career development and personal growth.

PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES

- Self-Motivated and Ability to Work with Little or No Supervision.
- Self confidence and Willingness to Learn.
- Honesty and Integrity

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Mathematics
- Further Mathematics
- Physics
- Applied Electricity
- Basic Technology

PERSONAL INFORMATION

•	Date of birth	05 October	er 1989

Sex MaleMarital status Single

• LGA Ibarapa Central

Religion ChristenState OyoNationality Nigerian

EDUCATION

INSTITUTION	QUALIFICATION OBTAINED	DATES
 Methodist Primary School, 	First school leaving certificate	1998
Isale-Oba Igboora		
• Methodist Grammer School,	Senior Secondary School Certificate	2004
Sagan-un Igboora		
• Wallant Computer College,	Diploma (Desktop Publishing)	2005
Mushin Lagos		
 University of Ibadan, 	BSc Mathematics	2014
 National Youth Service Corp 	, NYSC	2016
Lagos Nigeria		

WORK EXPERIENCE

• Raodhot College, Offin, Ikorodu, Lagos. (2017 till date)

Position: Mathematics educator

• Starling school Lekki, Lagos Island. (2015 – Oct., 2016).

Position: Mathematics educator

• Sweet Savour Model Schools Ojoo Ibadan.(2014-2015)

Position: Mathematics educator

RESPONSIBILITIES

✓ Develop schemes of work and lesson plans in line with curriculum objectives.

- ✓ Facilitate learning by establishing a relationship with pupils, and by their organisation of learning resources and the classroom learning environment.
- ✓ Develop and foster the appropriate skills and social abilities to enable the optimum development of children, according to age, ability and aptitude.
- ✓ Link pupils' knowledge to earlier learning and develop ways to encourage it further, and challenge and inspire pupils to help them deepen their knowledge and understanding.
- Marvelous Mike Press, Mushin Lagos (2013 2014).

Position: Graphics Instructor/Design

• Infinity Press, Ikeja Lagos (2010 – 2011).

Position: Graphics Instructor/Design

SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- Leadership and effective supervision skills
- Performance evaluation skills.
- Decision-making skills
- Time management skills.
- Team building skills.
- Analytical and problem-solving skills
- Effective verbal, listening and communication skills.
- Stress management skills
- Strong People management skills
- Excellent IT skills such as
 - o Micro soft office: word, excel, power point etc
 - o Graphics Applications: Coreldraw, Photoshop, Pagemaker, Print-artist etc
 - Letex
 - Auto desk inventor
 - Software installation
 - o Proficient in the use of Interactive white board

HOBBIES

• Reading, Football and surfing the internet

REFERENCES

 Pastor M O Akinlade Christ Apostolic Church Oke-Alafia Samonda, Ibadan.

Tel: 08033690167

Hon. Rufai
 Executive Chairman,
 Ibarapa Central Local Government, Igboora.
 Tel:08033002522

Prof. A Ojebode

H.O.D Communication and Language Art University of Ibadan, Ibadan, Oyo State.

Tel: 08056414798

Mr. Akeju

Asst., Lecturer, Mathematics Department University of Ibadan, Ibadan Oyo Stat

Tel: 07039249444

